# Caspar Abelmann

# I'll be your data analyst.

My skillset is tailored towards data analysis and visual design. I have broad knowledge and experience with this in both work and hobby and always strive to perfect these skills. I've also gained great leadership ability through my hobby as online moderator and playing competitive team-based videogames. I easily flow into a team and can make anyone feel included. I keep people up to date and try to arrange for solutions if problems arise.

## **EXPERIENCE**

### **Administrative Data Analyst Student**

@ DAATLAB

July 2021 - Feb. 2022

Learnt the intricacies surrounding data visualisation in Power BI, not only using DAX but also gaining deeper knowledge of design and focus to create a clear picture to stakeholders.

Held daily stand-ups and closely worked together with colleagues to keep track of our progress. Helping those that fall behind.

#### **Artist**

@ University Utrecht

Sept. 2018 - Feb. 2019

Closely worked together with 9 developer students to create a promotional video featuring the UCrowd Crowd Simulation program.

Communicated directly with the client who was very pleased with the result

### **3D Artist**

@ Movares

Feb. 2018 - July 2018

Worked alongside 2 artists to create 3D models for a large scale visualisation of the Utrecht canal bridge project.

Trusted to be the first artist to create a base for a car driving simulator which spreads awareness of the dangers of train overpasses.

### **VOLUNTARY**

### Online Community Moderator

@ Wabbitface

Mar. 2015 - Jan. 2016

Managed over 75 daily users with a 3000 user active player base.

Note taker at weekly meetings. Bringing insight on stakeholder wants and needs.

Trusted with powerful server-wide tools, received multiple promotions and was project leader of several large scale projects.

### **Online Community Moderator**

@ Project Genesis

Jul. 2020 - Jul. 2021

Managed a Discord server of a total of  $750~\mathrm{users}.$  Solving conflicts between members.

Direct communication with the developers and organised bug reports.

### **Online Community Moderator**

@ Sector's Edge

Dec. 2020 - Jul. 2021

Managed a Discord server featuring over 1800 users. Solving issues and keeping peace both in the server and in-game.

Project leader of a new gamemode map.

## **LEARNING**

### Coding Python & Kotlin

Web scraping, Visualisation App Development

#### German Language

Hochdeutsch

### Personal Improvement

Mindfulness, Voice training

## **EDUCATION**

### Game Artist (MBO-4)

@ Grafisch Lyceum Utrecht

Sept. 2014 - Jul. 2019

Used Adobe Photoshop, Autodesk 3DS  $\mbox{\rm Max}$  and Unity Game Engine to create videogames.

Took on project leader roles in many projects.

### **HOBBIES**

3D Printing Cryptocurrencies Modifying hardware Competitive videogames

### LANGUAGES

**Dutch** Native

**English** Proficient

### CONTACT

Email Caspar.Q.Abelmann@Hotmail.com
Phone (+31) 06 534 234 30

Address Netherlands, 3888LL Uddel

**LinkedIn** /in/CasparAbelmann/

